let questions12 = [
    {
        numb: 1,
        question: "alone",
        answer: "A. allein",
        options: [
            "A. allein",
            "B. zusammen",
            "C. begleitet",
            "D. gesellig"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 2,
        question: "apartment",
        answer: "B. Wohnung",
        options: [
            "A. Haus",
            "B. Wohnung",
            "C. Zimmer",
            "D. Büro"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 3,
        question: "article",
        answer: "C. Artikel",
        options: [
            "A. Buch",
            "B. Notiz",
            "C. Artikel",
            "D. Anzeige"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 4,
        question: "artist",
        answer: "D. Künstler",
        options: [
            "A. Schriftsteller",
            "B. Musiker",
            "C. Tänzer",
            "D. Künstler"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 5,
        question: "attitude",
        answer: "A. Einstellung",
        options: [
            "A. Einstellung",
            "B. Verhalten",
            "C. Aussehen",
            "D. Stimmung"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 6,
        question: "to compare",
        answer: "B. vergleichen",
        options: [
            "A. trennen",
            "B. vergleichen",
            "C. bewerten",
            "D. entscheiden"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 7,
        question: "to judge",
        answer: "C. beurteilen",
        options: [
            "A. ignorieren",
            "B. vermeiden",
            "C. beurteilen",
            "D. schätzen"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 8,
        question: "magazine",
        answer: "A. Zeitschrift",
        options: [
            "A. Zeitschrift",
            "B. Zeitung",
            "C. Buch",
            "D. Broschüre"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 9,
        question: "material",
        answer: "D. Material",
        options: [
            "A. Werkzeug",
            "B. Maschine",
            "C. Ausrüstung",
            "D. Material"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 10,
        question: "meal",
        answer: "B. Mahlzeit",
        options: [
            "A. Gericht",
            "B. Mahlzeit",
            "C. Snack",
            "D. Getränk"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 11,
        question: "method",
        answer: "A. Methode",
        options: [
            "A. Methode",
            "B. Problem",
            "C. Plan",
            "D. Idee"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 12,
        question: "neighbor",
        answer: "B. Nachbar",
        options: [
            "A. Freund",
            "B. Nachbar",
            "C. Kollege",
            "D. Verwandter"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 13,
        question: "professional",
        answer: "C. professionell",
        options: [
            "A. Amateur",
            "B. Schüler",
            "C. professionell",
            "D. Anfänger"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 14,
        question: "profit",
        answer: "D. Gewinn",
        options: [
            "A. Verlust",
            "B. Ausgabe",
            "C. Schulden",
            "D. Gewinn"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 15,
        question: "quality",
        answer: "B. Qualität",
        options: [
            "A. Menge",
            "B. Qualität",
            "C. Preis",
            "D. Stil"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 16,
        question: "shape",
        answer: "A. Form",
        options: [
            "A. Form",
            "B. Farbe",
            "C. Größe",
            "D. Textur"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 17,
        question: "space",
        answer: "D. Raum",
        options: [
            "A. Objekt",
            "B. Möbel",
            "C. Bild",
            "D. Raum"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 18,
        question: "stair",
        answer: "B. Treppe",
        options: [
            "A. Tür",
            "B. Treppe",
            "C. Fenster",
            "D. Balkon"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 19,
        question: "symbol",
        answer: "C. Symbol",
        options: [
            "A. Name",
            "B. Buchstabe",
            "C. Symbol",
            "D. Zahl"
        ]
    },
    {
        numb: 20,
        question: "thin",
        answer: "A. dünn",
        options: [
            "A. dünn",
            "B. dick",
            "C. breit",
            "D. schmal"
        ]
    }
];
